well it is only the third time I've seen
an acoustic neuroma have an issue with
inter cerebral hematoma causing inter
cranial pressure well we all know that
eighth cranial nerve you know that can
be finicky although the acoustical
neuromas are benign you have to be
careful with those vestibular schomas
about schomas like schomas all day every
day as long as I have to do with
pituitary adenomas or himal blastomas or
anything near the cranial feral duct all
right what about this doctor what about
gasta multiform H you're joking right I
don't know am I no of course he's not we
all love gbms right give me a break GBM
I'm a GBM guy you know we're doctors so
how was your brain
surgery beat
that beat
that
all
right
be
that
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
Dr pton doctor Doogie doctor Dr pton
please doctor
no be
that who are those guys
Randy
beat
that when you dance the dance of love
everyone from the heavens above they
look down upon you and
smile
beat
that
that notice the
Cherry
beat
that
what got too much stuff in his mouth I
can't hear what the stuff in your mouth
I can't understand yeah it's definitely
stuff in your mouth I can't understand
what you're saying it's the
stuff bacon bacon sandwich uh two two
words we got to play with the we got to
play with
the
puyy
guys chocolate
labs here for you to roll around and
play chocolate labs lots of fun and we
are here to stay
chocol